Gary Young: Howdy go.
Wade Brown: Howdy, howdy!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Ahoy!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So we're missing our Game Master, aren't we?
Wade Brown: Yup.
David Mendenhall: Is that what's.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do you in Greece?
David Mendenhall: I don't think so.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Nope.
David Mendenhall: Not according to his LinkedIn.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Good morning, Stephane, how are you?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm good, how are you?
David Mendenhall: Did you get to see the eclipse?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No.
David Mendenhall: Oh, that's too bad.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I was in the pool hall.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Shooting some bull.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's my, secret, hobby, is billiards.
Wade Brown: secret.
David Mendenhall: Means, like… like, billiards?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, billiards, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Nice.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do I mean, secret? No, it's not really a secret.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Just saying.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: To make it more interesting than it really is.
David Mendenhall: Are you, could you wipe the table with the rest of us? Are you, like, really good?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm not that good, meaning I don't run the tables systematically.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But I can, eventually, if the layout is not too bad.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah, okay, so you could cream us.
Wade Brown: Yeah, sometimes I don't scratch. Sometimes.
David Mendenhall: Maybe you could give us all lessons.
David Mendenhall: Always wanted to be really good at billiards.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what YouTube is for, my friend.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: the,
David Mendenhall: I've watched those videos.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But it… that's the thing about Billiard, it's very deceiving. It looks super simple, right? You're like, hey, I've got a queue, there's a ball, here I should…
David Mendenhall: Yup. I agree.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, but it's, in fact, extremely complex, so it's one of those things you have to, you know, shoot a million ball, and then you'll start starting to get it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And, and get results. But it's still important to understand the fundamentals, I suppose. It's just really hard to start getting results from applying them.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: If that makes any sense.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade Brown: That does. I mean, I know, like, the…
Wade Brown: you know, the concept of aiming for the dots, but I still haven't been able to apply that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right. What's this?
Kostadis Roussos: What are we talking about?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Video. Biddyot.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I, I play billiard.
Wade Brown: Do you play Snooker at all?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So I tried Snooker, and to be honest, I find it mostly boring, in that…
Wade Brown: That's fair. I…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I mean, it's great for your fundamentals, but it's also… So hard to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: shoot straight on a snooker table, because, you know, it's so big, that you can't… you can't really afford, like, you know, side spins and… and everything that makes American Pool interesting.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I'll be damned.
Wade Brown: Gladys Yanks did something right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why, why would you be damned, Kostadis?
Kostadis Roussos: I did not know that you played pool.
Wade Brown: It's a secret.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, it's a secret.
Gary Young: The secret from everybody.
Wade Brown: I get that one.
David Mendenhall: Everyone? Yeah.
Wade Brown: Dangerous to go alone.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so… I think everybody decided… we, we, so…
Wade Brown: Charging into a house for gas.
David Mendenhall: I don't know what Zoom is doing to your face, but, like…
David Mendenhall: What, what do you, like, have here?
Wade Brown: He shaved his beard?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I have my beard.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: I…
Wade Brown: Got some dirt on your chin?
David Mendenhall: I don't know, maybe, like, turn off the touch up your per- your appearance?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that what's going on?
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, I've just played with these things.
Gary Young: Video filter? Is that what you think it is?
Kostadis Roussos: How's that?
David Mendenhall: Okay, now I can… now I can… yeah. Yeah, it's hair. Okay.
David Mendenhall: I'll go with it.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm, like, very nervous.
David Mendenhall: Pine looks good.
Wade Brown: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. You now have to, like, take a screenshot and send it to me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's peg…
Kostadis Roussos: Like, I mean, you have to take the screenshot and send it to me, dude, like, now I'm curious.
Wade Brown: There we go.
Wade Brown: That's what I was looking.
David Mendenhall: Did you clip it?
David Mendenhall: Wade.
Wade Brown: That's what you were looking for, right?
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, that actually is funny.
Kostadis Roussos: Wade, when he's laughing, that actually works in a very amusing way.
Wade Brown: It's, yeah, I'm gonna turn that off now.
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's play.
Wade Brown: Oh, crap.
David Mendenhall: Huh?
Wade Brown: Oh, Pride Mode.
David Mendenhall: Oh my gosh. I guess I've not played with Zoom as much as you have.
Wade Brown: Alright.
Wade Brown: Doops. It's got animal avatars, too, if you're really bored.
David Mendenhall: Video and effects settings. Okay, now, now I'm going all in. What does this say? Allow facial effects. Agree. Oh, wow.
David Mendenhall: There we go.
Gary Young: So this is for all the furries out there.
David Mendenhall: That can be a cow.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Ugh.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What have you done?
Kostadis Roussos: What are you done?
David Mendenhall: What do these video filters do? What's this do? Oh, wow, I can have.
Wade Brown: Yeah, that's… that's how you get the mustache.
David Mendenhall: Amazing.
David Mendenhall: Okay, yeah.
Wade Brown: Yeah. Computers were a mistake.
Kostadis Roussos: You were what?
Wade Brown: computers.
Kostadis Roussos: We're…
Wade Brown: or a mistake.
Kostadis Roussos: I agree.
David Mendenhall: Studio effects.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You put a loading bar on your head.
Kostadis Roussos: I… I have… I… I… I prepared.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course, you guys, as this tradition will go in a completely different direction, where I was completely unprepared, which is totally cool, but I just want you to know I have prepared.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you're gonna go to the Morning Lord's Spire in the morning.
David Mendenhall: We gotta do the comp.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Pretty big assumption. Now we gotta go somewhere else, guys.
Wade Brown: Yeah!
Gary Young: Well, I mean…
David Mendenhall: I got green lips.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I think, I think, I think we know, we did Brewberry's thing, we did a Rudin's thing.
David Mendenhall: We gotta do Delphina's thing. I agree.
Wade Brown: And I need my turtle soup.
Kostadis Roussos: And… and we have to do the turtle soup.
Wade Brown: I hear it's great.
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Gary Young: in the image.
Gary Young: Although I put turtle soup in the image, I wasn't quite sure that you really wanted to go all the way to turtle.
Wade Brown: Not harmful.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not…
David Mendenhall: Applied.
Kostadis Roussos: Portal, it's not soup made of portals.
Wade Brown: Yes, it is. Just like Girl Scout cookies are cookies made of Girl Scouts. Well, I mean.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, Valfeet, you know, Sova?
Kostadis Roussos: you've got to give us a take on this. I mean, you're ultimately, you know, this is your culture. As you say, it's made with turtles.
Kostadis Roussos: We won't… we won't judge.
Kostadis Roussos: As we all judge.
Wade Brown: We won't judge out loud.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's… we're all judging you now, Sovo.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know if that, that, that landed, but okay. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, I, I think I shared with you guys… here, let me just do it here.
Gary Young: You bet.
Wade Brown: Yeah, the summary?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: in my voice.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, your auto-generated voice.
Kostadis Roussos: using the shittier version of the model than I wanted. But anyway, I…
Kostadis Roussos: I finally have gotten my tools to finally work the way I want them to, so I'm very happy.
David Mendenhall: It only took me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Whoa.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Until next week.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And then you want them to do something else, you know? It's a never-ending loop, Kostadis. You know it.
Kostadis Roussos: Anyhow…
Gary Young: I wanted to make it… have it make square vault doors.
Gary Young: That is not something that's possible, just to be clear.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's a house-coded safety.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so,
Gary Young: read those, those pictures, I could not get it to mix, you know, rectangular vault tours.
Wade Brown: In painting.
Gary Young: Yeah, the door jamb would be rectangular, but the.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Gary Young: be around.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to do one thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I just noticed, on the strategy image.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I'm looking…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That looks very funny.
Kostadis Roussos: We need to do something.
Kostadis Roussos: We're… it's,
Kostadis Roussos: Cool. I did actually, load everything correctly. Guys, give me one second, I need to get myself a soda to drink.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So recently, I've started making cocktails as well.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: about, like, a Boston shaker and, you know, an ice machine.
Wade Brown: Getting fancy.
David Mendenhall: Do you get, like, pebble ice, or, like, crust ice?
Wade Brown: Where do you got?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I make some pretty mean cocktails, like, old-fashioned, and
David Mendenhall: That's a good one.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Negronis.
Kostadis Roussos: For some reason, I thought you would be in the US today, because it's sales kickoff.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, no, no, I don't go to Vegas. I try not to, anyway.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay. So, it is the morning, and,
Kostadis Roussos: you know, the fact that Vukradin intends to announce is the name of his latest band.
Kostadis Roussos: and the impromptu performance he put at…
Kostadis Roussos: At the, along with, Lathander. He's the latest cleric.
David Mendenhall: Athena.
Kostadis Roussos: Velphine at the Moonstone Mask, has created quite… has created quite the stir at the Spire of the Morning Lord.
Gary Young: Yes, well, they also invited me to come to the spire, so I am there. I am coming to provide the sermon of the morning.
David Mendenhall: the server.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm really…
David Mendenhall: Playing first, or are we… are we creeping first?
Gary Young: Sermon first.
Gary Young: Followed by music and sacraments.
Wade Brown: It's a Unitarian service.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, okay. Alright, hold on, I need to… I have notes, so I need to get them out.
Gary Young: I've prepared the sermon, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, good lord.
David Mendenhall: I'm excited.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I want to hear this.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, they're getting out.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, hold on, hold on, give me one second.
Wade Brown: No, this is the way the GM goes off-script for just to troll you now.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's one more thing I want to bring up. I just want to bring up. Zoom…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, now I need to do one more thing.
Kostadis Roussos: I have so many damn tools that I use that sometimes I get lost.
Wade Brown: Happens with age, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: It's dawn.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, well, of course it's dawn, because when else would a sermon by the Morning Lord,
Gary Young: works.
Kostadis Roussos: Me done. I'll cook, you, you, you arrive at the doors, at the Spire's threshold.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's a whole bunch of clerics, at the doors.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Kostadis Roussos: You can see a whole bunch of, you can see a whole bunch of factions around.
Kostadis Roussos: You can now roll some perception checks and awareness checks to see what's going on.
Gary Young: Sure.
Gary Young: 28 insight.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you roll with 20 insights?
David Mendenhall: Natural One.
Gary Young: 28 insights.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What are we ruling perception? Okay, I've got minus one, man, I mean…
David Mendenhall: My naivete is peaking.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: 15.
Wade Brown: Site plus 10, Jesus.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so,
Kostadis Roussos: You can see… okay, so who is it that you can see? You can see, skeptical otheranderite clerics at the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Who are this guy?
Gary Young: Cool love.
Kostadis Roussos: Guess.
Gary Young: Suddenly.
Wade Brown: A drow cleric of Lathander?
Kostadis Roussos: a drought cleric of Defender who… I mean, you could go ask, I'm just telling you, you notice that they're skeptic… they're looking at you with a certain amount of skepticism.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Gary Young: I'll go and look at them with my.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, let me just, let me tell you what…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: and non-believers.
Kostadis Roussos: As you're kind of walking in there, and there's, like, you know, There's, like, a whole…
Kostadis Roussos: I just want to give you the lay of the land of what you're seeing as you walk into the building, right?
Gary Young: Huh.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice, several lovyaturite agents in the shadows.
Kostadis Roussos: Some love, some lovely, love.
Kostadis Roussos: Loviatar is the goddess…
Gary Young: Followers of Love Via Tar.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the followers of Love, who are the gods of pain, you know, so your whole searing pain…
Wade Brown: Your sacrament is applicable.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, he's stealing the sacrament.
Kostadis Roussos: It's heretical.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Right, you also can tell…
Kostadis Roussos: You also can… who else can you see? Let me just, bring up the list.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I'm a little bit slow today, because my…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, are the skepticals, are they, like, in a group, or are they just scattered around the room?
Kostadis Roussos: They're scattered around.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Gary Young: So is there anyone that they look to as a person of authority?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, let me… let me give you the rest of the crew, I'm not done. Hold on. I'm sorry, guys. My brain… my brain's a little bit slow this morning, because I… I woke up by jet lag.
Kostadis Roussos: And who else?
Kostadis Roussos: There's… you also see, so, also, to your surprise, see, Lord Nevermember.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
Gary Young: We're done for a minute there.
David Mendenhall: I mean, it's a concert?
Kostadis Roussos: You also see a crowd… Faithful and curious.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: That's sort of the… that's sort of the audience, that you're seeing. Everybody seems to have arrived very early in the morning.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
Kostadis Roussos: So, like, this is, you know, turned into a thing. So, you know, you can enter, and you've got this a choice. You can walk in, like, have an avatar, eyes blazing, you could pause to bless the crowd, you can…
Kostadis Roussos: let Vukraden try to work the crowd a little bit, you know, do his shtick.
Kostadis Roussos: You can ignore them and head straight through the doors, it's up to you, right?
Gary Young: Oh, I am.
Kostadis Roussos: So just to be clear, like, so the way… the vibe to it is that you're walking into this temple, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And there's… and there's all these… it's… it's not empty, right? Like, people… and there's, like…
Kostadis Roussos: factions within factions. These are the ones you recognize. You do get the sense that there are more factions, and
Gary Young: And I'm wearing my new gleaming white dragon plate nail.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, you haven't picked it up, you're picking it up on the way out.
Gary Young: On the way out.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: It… well, I mean, canonically, we said it was going to be ready on the way out.
Gary Young: I see. Okay, well, we'll just, retcon some things a little bit later.
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's fine.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Just fulfill that goals. No, that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: decisions and…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Hold on, I'm casting so much energy on myself, and so my eyes light up with light.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: As I touched Valfini's shoulder.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And then I, there's a phantom sound coming from the door as we walk in.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's, ominous Whispers, just for theatrics.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, but, you know, so just to be clear, just before you arrived, just to… we don't have to retcon anything, the, the guy from Dragons R Us scales?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Dragonscales are us. I was so excited about you showing up that he produced… he showed up with the Dragonscale armor.
Gary Young: Which is a great advertisement for his business.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he wants the blessing of Lathander, like, he's, like, he's really…
Gary Young: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He's one… he's one of the devout, and he's thinking that if you're gonna give a sermon, and that you… that this armor… and he… so he spent all night… he spent all night working on it, it's… it's… it's assembled, and, you know, he's… as you show up, he's, like, fitting it on you, very excited, or he showed up here.
Gary Young: of it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so you've got your, you know, you've got your armor. This, of course, causes an even bigger stir as people see you put on dragon-scale armor.
Gary Young: Yeah. Well, I mean, it shows that we're, you know, not to be trifled with, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I mean, you know, there's, like, whispers and commentary.
Kostadis Roussos: And the owner is very proud of himself.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: And my eyes are certainly quite visible to, Yeah, the onlookers?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I mean, you know, yes. I mean, as you look around, people can see the gleaming eyes.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: you know, what do you want to do? Like, seriously, this isn't exactly the time and place to sit down and chat. Your brother Aldrich is waiting for you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, it's how you want to work… how do you want to work the room, so…
Gary Young: So…
Kostadis Roussos: I gave you some options.
Kostadis Roussos: I gave you some perform… so just to make this clear, right? You walk in like an Alvatar blazing, you roll a religion check.
Kostadis Roussos: You pause to bless the crowd, roll a persuasion, let Vukkridan do it.
Gary Young: I'm going to raise my hand up high.
Gary Young: Casting a daylight spell, and say, it is time for the morning sermon.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay,
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so, you walk in, and Brother Aldrick has asked that you first, before you go and deliver the sermon, you come and talk to him.
Gary Young: Really?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yeah. I mean, he looks at that and goes, there's a private receiving chamber, right?
Kostadis Roussos: You weren't supposed to do that. He kind of goes like this and ponders, you know, all the liturgical and ceremonial elements that you have forgotten and wonders, but he's in a good mood.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: Oh, am I supposed to roll a religion to see what I'm forgetting? I… I probably know what I'm doing,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. No, no, you're doing your thing, right? I mean… You, you, you're.
Gary Young: I'm not doing anything much.
David Mendenhall: You're… Personally, yeah.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yo, let me just… you're not…
David Mendenhall: Your religion isn't his religion.
Wade Brown: Yeah. It's a new religion.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, actually, sorry, this is important. Are you trying to be cannot… are you trying to follow the sacraments as the curtain offender, or are you riffing on the Church of the Searing Pain?
Gary Young: I am leaning into the Church of the Syrian Pain, but I do know the room.
Gary Young: And so the question is, like, how do we draw them in? Okay. And so… You, you, you…
Gary Young: You drop the bomb on them subtly.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, alright, so I'll just say that generally people go with the light spell, To announce the circuit.
Gary Young: like…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but you went the next level with Daylight.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, just, you know, with that.
David Mendenhall: Hey, it wasn't Sunbeam.
Gary Young: That's, that's a lot.
Wade Brown: I'll laugh after this one, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: People weren't dying, so I guess, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: Is that a fair… is that a fair way to characterize it? You know, like, the original normal…
David Mendenhall: There is no, there is no undead here.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, alright.
David Mendenhall: We took care of that problem.
Kostadis Roussos: There's enough clerics here that there's certainly no undead. All right. You do make a pause… roll your religion… what did you roll for your religion?
Gary Young: 16.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, you made a… you made a very positive impression. You can see the crowd is… is… is…
Kostadis Roussos: quite pleased to see you, you know, there's, like, they're in awe of your spellcasting. It's not very often people see a daylight spell in the middle of the day inside of the Church of Thunder. Some of the people.
Gary Young: It's dawn. It's dawn, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it does make quite a bit, like, you know, it lights up the entire chamber. Some people kind of squint, and I'm assuming, you know, you admire their pain for just a moment.
Wade Brown: D.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So I'll lean over, Vaspina, I'll whisper and I hear, but let's make sure we collect the nations at the end of the sermon.
Gary Young: Oh, I haven't planned.
David Mendenhall: But he has many plans, yes. No, I'm just waiting for the plans. I am here to serve, by the way, anything you want me to do, just… just ask.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, so am I.
Gary Young: Who's chatting? Where's the ping coming from?
Gary Young: Oh, okay, nevermind.
Gary Young: Alright, so,
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Gary Young: Let's talk to me before I go up to do the survey?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right, yeah. Right, so he has… and, you know, and it turns out it's a…
Kostadis Roussos: You, you, you're, you're… it turns out it's Brother Aldrich and several, of the,
Kostadis Roussos: Several of the clerics that…
David Mendenhall: So, Phoenix. Old person?
Gary Young: Perfect.
David Mendenhall: No? Okay, alright, just say the word. We got… I got it ready.
Kostadis Roussos: As you… even Brukerdin's perception notices that nobody seems to be armed. After all, it is in the middle.
David Mendenhall: Well, there's, you know, maybe, you know, I don't know what he's got planned.
Kostadis Roussos: This is easier.
Gary Young: does involve.
David Mendenhall: Maybe he wants to inflict pain, you know, like, cold person's great for inflicting pain.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, yes, we know that.
Gary Young: Promoting the band, And drumming up business sales for the rooms.
David Mendenhall: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and the bathrooms, right?
Gary Young: Yes, yes. Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I mean, you know, so, Brother Aldrick is, is very… he's, he's…
Kostadis Roussos: He's got, like, this concerned look on his face. He's heard… he goes, I've, you know, I've heard… I've heard of the blessed temple that you've built in Phandalin.
Gary Young: Why, yes, that's glorious.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but, I have a question. You keep talking about this blessing that… what does it mean? What is the meaning of the blessing?
Gary Young: It allows us to gain a deeper appreciation of the glory and power of the morning Lord.
Kostadis Roussos: But, so, okay…
Kostadis Roussos: So, so you're saying this is… this is… this is not about the pain, this is about your redemption and your understanding of the Morning Lord's, path, right?
Gary Young: Why, yes, of course, of course.
Gary Young: We must gain a deeper spiritual communion.
Gary Young: Wes. Good morning, Lord.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll a DC… Roll a charisma check.
Gary Young: Charisma checks.
Gary Young: Does that mean… Persuasion, persuasion?
Kostadis Roussos: Persuasion, persuasion, sorry.
Gary Young: squeeze it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, sir.
David Mendenhall: Zoom name with the persuasion, yeah.
David Mendenhall: I told you!
David Mendenhall: Sure, bargains.
Gary Young: inspiration or something?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, if you can have a Bardic inspiration, like, you know, I'm assuming you're giving out Bardic inspirations, Rukutin?
Gary Young: Yeah, what's the product inspiration?
David Mendenhall: You just added… you only get to add a D8, sorry.
Wade Brown: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, you got a 5.
Gary Young: So I get a D4 from my thing, and a D8 from his, and so that makes it an 8.
Kostadis Roussos: No, that bad.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: The, the, that, that, you're, you're, you're,
Kostadis Roussos: Brother Aldrick is not… is not impressed. He seems a little bit…
Kostadis Roussos: He seemed, he seemed… Let's see… he seems a little bit, disappointed.
Kostadis Roussos: Does anybody, Does anybody want to try to help her so that she gets another role?
David Mendenhall: We're all helping.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I know, but who wants to do the helping? Like, which one of you?
Gary Young: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: That's who gets an advantage.
David Mendenhall: Teenage choice.
Kostadis Roussos: Ralphine, who do you want to step in to help you?
Gary Young: Roomberg.
David Mendenhall: Bourd, of course!
Wade Brown: Bit of a star.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What can they do?
Kostadis Roussos: So, I mean, you… I mean, you can make some… so you can roll with Advantage. Roll again, Gary.
Kostadis Roussos: So I'm assuming Brewberry kind of does his thing, and, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, I've got my eyes gleaming with light, and and again, ominous whispers coming from the back of the room with my thematic.
David Mendenhall: 12? Alright, did you… I get the same bonus as well.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay, okay. So, alder. Keep your.
David Mendenhall: Inspiration, so you can use it again.
Gary Young: inspirations, that would be 18.
David Mendenhall: 18.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Got it.
Kostadis Roussos: On a success, Eldrich accepts your theological points.
Kostadis Roussos: He says, well, I'm happy to see that you're doing this, but I warn you to stay away from this path of pain. This is not the Lathander's way.
Kostadis Roussos: That's.
Gary Young: God.
Kostadis Roussos: And then…
Gary Young: What do you mean by that?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so before you can get that, one of… another sun priest interrupts.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, one of the priests who's sitting around, and you notice he's kind of scarred, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: And asks, is pain the point or the healing?
Gary Young: The light is the point.
Gary Young: He is the Morning Lord, the Lord of Light.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that one's good.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Imagine life taught you that healing can be painful.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, okay, you… you're, so you're going… so, so you said the Lanthander is the point, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that yours?
Gary Young: The light is the point. He is the God of light.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so, but yes, but why do you insist on the pain?
Gary Young: Because…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But healing doesn't come cheap, my friend.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sometimes it used to… That's the mess.
Gary Young: Embrace the fullness of the light, you must experience it in its totality.
Gary Young: Otherwise, it's just a pale shadow.
Gary Young: of Shadow.
Kostadis Roussos: But then why is… what is the purpose of the healing?
Gary Young: Well then… Our Lord has great, you know, like, ambitions for us.
Gary Young: On this world, and therefore, we must be able to then see the lit path.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that was, that was good. Alright, roll a, Persuasion.
Gary Young: up again.
David Mendenhall: I'll give you an hour of inspiration.
Gary Young: With Advantage or not.
Wade Brown: Whew.
Kostadis Roussos: with… With Advantage, I'm assuming somebody's helping you.
Gary Young: Natural 20.
David Mendenhall: Well done.
Wade Brown: Persuaded.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm lucky.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, brother, what did you… what did you roll? Did you…
Gary Young: money.
Kostadis Roussos: He rolled a natural 20. Wow.
Kostadis Roussos: So, he's very… he smiles, and you immediately gather that the other cleric was there to trap you, but that you managed to thread the trap.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, they were trying to trap you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Gary Young: By doing a good job with my theology.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, so he's very pleased. He makes the sign of the morning, Lord, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you are now in… so with that, you are in a packed hall down through the windows, right?
David Mendenhall: Going to the Sanhedrin, man, this is…
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Do you get some inspiration on this one, Kostadis?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I mean…
Gary Young: Look here.
Kostadis Roussos: What? I thought this would be fun, right?
David Mendenhall: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? So… So you, you're, you know, you, you walk in, and, and there's…
Kostadis Roussos: There's the congregation is there, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, you're, you're… and, the congregation is there for you to give your sermon. And, you know, there's… as you look around, or all your investigation or insight.
Gary Young: Okay, and I put an image in the, in the…
Wade Brown: Heh.
Gary Young: Story so far.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we'll just go there.
Gary Young: inside of…
David Mendenhall: Discord?
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: Inside of 15, plus some bonuses, perhaps?
Gary Young: I still get my D4, right?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I just saw the brewery one.
Wade Brown: Yeah, he's so happy.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I am happy.
David Mendenhall: in robes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: My friend is on the stage, you know, all eyes on him.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He's about to illuminate them with his divine message.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: That'd be good for business.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And let's see who else,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I do ponder why some question the way that he sets forth, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. You also notice that Perrin is there.
Gary Young: Barrett?
Kostadis Roussos: Perrin.
David Mendenhall: Karen?
Kostadis Roussos: Parent, parent, parent. Oh, yeah, the guy.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I will claim.
Kostadis Roussos: Iron Alligander.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: claims that we owe him the thing.
Wade Brown: And yo.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's the next.
Wade Brown: Close, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, there you go.
David Mendenhall: Oh, that guy.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So he's there, you told him to be there.
Gary Young: Yeah. Right.
David Mendenhall: Right, because we're cutting the deal. Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so he's there, so… Okay.
Gary Young: Ready for… ready for the sermon?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, please.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Now I am.
Gary Young: Children of the dawn, gaze upon the rising sun and no true power.
Gary Young: Lathander is not a soft god of quiet comfort or gentle reprieve. He is the blinding radiance that cuts through the stagnant dark and shatters the slumber of the world.
Gary Young: Darkness does not yield to meekness, nor does the night retreat before trembling hands. Light is an absolute force, unyielding, fierce, and searing.
Gary Young: When the first rays of morning pierce the sky, they do not negotiate with the shadows. They destroy them, exposing every hidden corruption and sweeping away the decay of the night with uncompromising glory.
Gary Young: To truly walk in the light of the Morning Lord, one must undergo the sacred sacrament of blinding light.
Gary Young: In this holy rite, the faithful cast off all comforting illusions and look unflinchingly into the incandescent glare of pure divinity, until the eye beholds only burning gold, and every shadow within the soul is utterly incinerated.
Gary Young: It is in a baptism of fire and brilliance that hardens the spirit into a conduit of divine radiance.
Gary Young: Through this sacrament, we are remade not as passive observers, but as living blazes.
Gary Young: Forged to carry the intolerable heat of Lathander's glory into every dark corner of this realm.
Gary Young: Let the heathens and the creature spawn of pitch black abyss.
Gary Young: Tremble at our approach. Armed with the searing wrath of the Dawnbringer, it is our holy duty to purge the wicked and reduce their blasphemies to ash.
Gary Young: We do not offer pity to those who cling to the dark, or quarter for the meek and weak, for to harbor shadow is to invite destruction.
Gary Young: Rise, warriors of the morning. Lift high your glowing crests.
Gary Young: And let the untamed power of Lathander incinerate every enemy of the dawn. Through light alone we dominate. Through light alone we conquer.
Gary Young: Now, behold, Lathander's death.
David Mendenhall: Well done.
Kostadis Roussos: That was extremely well done.
Wade Brown: I think I'm changing religions.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, so…
David Mendenhall: We are Lathander's death.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: That just works, and so…
Gary Young: And of course, you know, like… and stop by the gift shop on the way out.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Don't forget to buy our merch.
Kostadis Roussos: the table.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Get your bathroom.
David Mendenhall: Do you want everyone to stare at the sun until they go blind? Is that the plan?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on, Rakuten, are you… That's the sacrament?
Kostadis Roussos: Well done.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: At some point, one, one lova… Low Viet… low yacht.
Wade Brown: threw it.
Kostadis Roussos: For a Greek who can pronounce words, loviate right. There. If I say with a Greek accent, I can say it. To the English, I can.
David Mendenhall: Well, Biardo is, like, the god of pain, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. Stands… Right.
Kostadis Roussos: In fact, and another one stands for another scream and denounces you. Pain is the maidens! The drow has dressed our sacramite in sacrament and called it
Kostadis Roussos: Holy… Alright.
Gary Young: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, my brothers, pain is simply the darkness you break through on your way to the dawn.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Gary Young: Dc-15 Constitution safe.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you just do?
Gary Young: I cast Blindness at him.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, now I have to go figure this out.
Kostadis Roussos: You literally cast him.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you… did you cast… okay, so, what do I have to roll? Right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to just,
David Mendenhall: I want to see the roll.
Kostadis Roussos: a 1.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That'll teach you.
Wade Brown: For the rest of his day.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Permanently blind.
Kostadis Roussos: That's not a permanent blindness, right?
Wade Brown: I don't want to think it is.
David Mendenhall: You're burning your spells, man!
Gary Young: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Duration, 1 minute.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Cast him out! Cast out the heathen!
Wade Brown: Believer.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, and so people are, you know, Okay, so, Gordon.
Kostadis Roussos: Several.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's right. If you're not a zealot, you get off the boat.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That doesn't rhyme. Doesn't work, does it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the other Loviatarite screams, this will… this, you know, this screams, like, goes, this will… you… you have stolen the sacraments of Loviatar! There will be consequences!
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Gary Young: How dare you to file the.
David Mendenhall: I don't think staring at the sun is a sacrament of Leviator.
Kostadis Roussos: Inflicting pain, though, is…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Isn't that what he did?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just…
David Mendenhall: friend.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they're religious fanatics, man.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that's.
Gary Young: The goal is the light, the pain is just a nice benefit, side benefit.
Kostadis Roussos: I hear you. Like, I want to be clear, your speech was eloquent, which is why, as they leave, you know, people just sort of stare at them with, like, contempt, so they, you know, they didn't make their point, but…
Kostadis Roussos: The fact that you blinded this guy did,
David Mendenhall: There will be comments!
Kostadis Roussos: I'm.
David Mendenhall: Offenses.
Kostadis Roussos: there will be consequences. I mean, you did just blind him.
David Mendenhall: Only for 1 minute.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But you call it, you call it blinding, I call it blessing. He blessed him with the holy light. You saw the light.
Wade Brown: It's an alternate way of taking the sacrament.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. So, alright, so let me just, da-da-da-da-da, alright.
David Mendenhall: Are we… do we get to play now? Can I play?
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Gary Young: Yeah, it's time for the band.
David Mendenhall: Time for some death metal, man. Alright, so… You gotta roll 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you guys are gonna… Get up and play.
David Mendenhall: Oops. Save me, Velcine, save me.
Gary Young: I don't that way.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: As the music is playing, I go around with a little basket.
David Mendenhall: I have advantage, right?
Gary Young: I need world performance, is that right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah. Or to remind…
Gary Young: Like, assisting you, and therefore you get advantage.
David Mendenhall: I don't know, whatever Kostadis says.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And I'll roll intimidation on… as I, you know, go around collecting donations, just to make sure that people…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, generous.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, so hold on. When you said the whole Lathander's death name, I had, like,
Kostadis Roussos: You know, there's uneasy laughter.
Kostadis Roussos: when you guys made that announcement, and as you start playing, there's, like, somebody gets up and starts cheering, and, like, there was, like, you get the impression that…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, like, the people are really excited, about it.
Kostadis Roussos: Mmm… I'm paying…
Wade Brown: These end up on stage.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right.
Gary Young: Common is not my native language, just to be clear.
David Mendenhall: Yes. What?
Gary Young: Common is not my native.
David Mendenhall: Common.
Gary Young: Undercomot is my name.
David Mendenhall: undercommon.
Gary Young: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: undercover.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
David Mendenhall: I think.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay… Alright, so, you start playing the music, right? Is that what I'm hearing?
Gary Young: So, so when we… yeah, when we play the music, what sort of roles do we need?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you're playing your music.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Kostadis Roussos: The performance. Performance.
Gary Young: And so, we'll have Dave roll, and then, like.
Gary Young: Does he have advantage, or, like, do we help him?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Gary Young: roll separately, what's the…
Kostadis Roussos: We rolled together, and the… You rule together, so if Dave succeeds… Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: It's kind of like a combination bonus, right? So if you… one… both of you succeed, then it counts.
Kostadis Roussos: More than if one of you succeeds.
David Mendenhall: Alright, Valpine, pull it off.
David Mendenhall: Thank you!
Gary Young: Correct. Saved it.
Kostadis Roussos: What did she get? What did she get?
Gary Young: I rolled a 17.
David Mendenhall: 17.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you roll a natural one?
David Mendenhall: I did.
Wade Brown: kid.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, God.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just tell you…
David Mendenhall: Belfine, do you want to sing in Undercommon? I speak Undercommon.
Wade Brown: Perfect.
Gary Young: I think that would be appropriate. I think that would be appropriate.
David Mendenhall: for another company.
David Mendenhall: Performance.
Kostadis Roussos: performance, you're there's scattered applause.
Kostadis Roussos: you know, as Rut Radin's performance leaves everybody a little bit uncertain about how to handle it.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, you know, someone starts humming a hymn that isn't one of the one… isn't what you're singing right now.
David Mendenhall: No, I mean, I think about, like…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, I'm not done.
David Mendenhall: Sorry. Okay, go ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know, the crowd, you know, once Falpina starts getting into it, the crowd kind of warms up to it, and there's, you know, swaying and cheering and…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, some… a few.
Gary Young: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, like, you know, there's enthusiasm.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Blueberry, as he looks over the crowd, notices that there's quite a few people dressed like him.
Gary Young: Good.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are they wearing a bathrobe?
Wade Brown: Heh.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Is it…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
David Mendenhall: Take off, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I go to them, and I, you know, I suggest that they buy a bathrobe, that it would look so much nicer, and it's soft and comfy. That's what true barbarians do.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and so… Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay. As, Soma is standing there, you know, someone, one of the supplicants notices you and says.
Kostadis Roussos: You are a protector of the… you are the protector of the Glades, and I was wondering if you would be willing to do a blessing for my garden, right in the middle of this whole religious festival.
Wade Brown: What, with the Merrill's staff?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I mean, yeah, she goes… that's what she says.
Wade Brown: I didn't know the staff could do blessings!
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, you're supposed to do bless spells.
Wade Brown: As a druid? I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I don't know, she's, like, kind of, like, seeing you, and, you know, she wants a blessing for her garden.
Wade Brown: I guess I can fake it.
Wade Brown: I'm not exactly trained in the religious arts, you know? Like, and I'm following there are these Luthandrians, or Lithandrinites, or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, I… yes. Well, I'm actually… the person explains that she's more syncretic in her religious beliefs. You know, there's plenty of gods, why worship only one? You know, you have to have gods for different purposes, and she notices you probably are a follower of Yalekai, so, you know, maybe you could ask for a little bit lessing from Yeliki.
Wade Brown: I… I think we can arrange that. What is it you would like out of your garden?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, just that it, it, it, it grows, and it's beautiful and lush, and that, you know, nothing…
Wade Brown: Life to Spring.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, she just, like.
Wade Brown: I can very much relate. Right.
Wade Brown: Religion roll or what?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, that just, yes, role of religion.
Wade Brown: Alright, minus one, let's go!
David Mendenhall: 15?
Wade Brown: 15, not bad, for a minus 1.
Kostadis Roussos: You successfully deliver the blessing.
Wade Brown: I faked it well enough.
Wade Brown: Soma's not that religious.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, yeah, I know, but you've got Merrill's staff, and rumors are spreading.
Wade Brown: Yeah, she'll come around, but, you know, after Valfina, she's thinking this Lothander's got the right idea.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so the concert… the concert goes well, and the service is over, and there's still some, there's still some folks sitting around, like, you know, you notice Cullen Sharp.
Wade Brown: Oh, who was Colin Sharp?
Kostadis Roussos: He's the How Smart Gaster guy.
Wade Brown: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh. Yeah. Alright.
Gary Young: Should we all take a moment to listen to, the music?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, God. Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We didn't do school.
Wade Brown: Oh, oh, that's what that Lord really is.
Gary Young: I don't know if we should do that.
Gary Young: on or off Zoom, but… From abyssal night, the darkness flees beyond.
David Mendenhall: Followed.
Gary Young: You don't up on your knees.
David Mendenhall: Mighty sword, descendant glory, born in Lord and grave.
Wade Brown: I hear two of yours.
David Mendenhall: Your sacred lights will save us all.
Kostadis Roussos: I, I wonder…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: of AI, huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Good. Nice one.
Wade Brown: Price increases are totally worth it.
Gary Young: That was worth it.
Kostadis Roussos: That was worth it.
Gary Young: I think…
David Mendenhall: RAM price increases are totally worth it. Oh, boy.
Kostadis Roussos: So, cullen, Cullen sees you.
Kostadis Roussos: And says, compliments you on your, new name.
Gary Young: Sweet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, on the group of you, it says, compliments you, and
Gary Young: band, yeah, yeah.
David Mendenhall: We are Lathander's dad!
David Mendenhall: Yeah!
Kostadis Roussos: He's… he's very impressed with it, and he mentions in passing that Mas Magastor always delivers the goods.
David Mendenhall: Right. Okay.
David Mendenhall: You go.
Wade Brown: Ominous, given the, you know… Trade route shut down, or whatever you want to call it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he, he, he, you know, he… and says that,
Kostadis Roussos: And then he, he reaches, he sees Blueberry's basket.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, Bourbury, you're going around trying to get money.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How much gold did I collect, by the way?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's awkward.
Gary Young: for profit.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, you don't have to answer now, but you are.
David Mendenhall: You're taking up donations for the church, right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, of course, yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It goes to the sender, yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
David Mendenhall: It's normal to make donations while you're at church, that's pretty typical.
Wade Brown: Tithing? Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Colin pulls out some coins.
Kostadis Roussos: Puts them over the basket, and…
Kostadis Roussos: Decides he doesn't want to donate.
Kostadis Roussos: And smiles at you, as if, like, the smile is the donation.
Gary Young: At me, or at him?
Kostadis Roussos: the, the, at,
Wade Brown: All of us?
Kostadis Roussos: At the group of you.
Kostadis Roussos: Nikki.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Who is this guy, again?
Kostadis Roussos: He's the… he's the, he's the Housemargaster guy with the green suit.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right.
Wade Brown: It's a great smile.
David Mendenhall: Who, you know, stopped… stopped the other guy from attacking us.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right, right. So I sort of tower over him, I make my voice boom with the matrixie again. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they're…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why aren't you donating?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… He, he, he looks at you, awkwardly. Alright, roll your intimidation.
Gary Young: The better question is, do you fear the light?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: There you go.
David Mendenhall: Well done.
Kostadis Roussos: He… I'm flexing…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: my muscle, you know, I'm doing the,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Rock thing, you know, with the…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: The pecs are going boom, boom.
Gary Young: Should we add the Bernic inspiration there, too?
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's not necessary. Colin is, colin notices that everybody's staring at him.
Kostadis Roussos: And he… he says, well, never let it be said. How smart Gaster is very… is very happy to donate to LaFander's,
Kostadis Roussos: Temple.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and applauds, Valfine's most recent
Kostadis Roussos: What's the word I'm looking for?
Gary Young: hypothesis.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: Apotheosis.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Kostadis Roussos: We're just looking for now.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes. Hollow flattery is not the.
David Mendenhall: One way to put it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: full, brother.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, spill the coins.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so… so he gives you the… the… the… he gives you some coins.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Some coins. No, I grabbed the whole pouch.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And I put it in the basket.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Thank you for your generosity, brother.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll a grapple check.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Grapple check, how do I roll that? Is that…
David Mendenhall: Attack role?
Gary Young: accepted.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I need to check, grapple. There's, like, the rules change for grapple.
Wade Brown: Thank you, J.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Isn't it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, a grappled creature can use this action to make a strength or dexterity against the grapple's escape DC.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Strength.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: I think, I think it's an attack roll.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so, here we go.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you roll?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Strength. I rolled Strength. Isn't that what I was supposed to do?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, what'd you rule? 20. Alright. Yeah, you are successfully able to grab the coins out of his hand and stuff them in the bag.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right, and that's what I do, and then I walk away.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Did you just… Did you just rob him?
Wade Brown: No.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Definitely? I didn't rob him? You know, I give him a nudge to be more generous.
Kostadis Roussos: Just when you ask that question, Colin says, of course not, Vukrudin. This was a generous donation that I was happy to make.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Absolutely.
David Mendenhall: Thank you for supporting Sander's death.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… he pauses and says, Vukriddin, as you know, we are all… we want the same things.
Gary Young: Right.
David Mendenhall: You want… Okay.
David Mendenhall: I love it.
Kostadis Roussos: We want the same things. I mean, you know, he's…
Kostadis Roussos: This is not… you want to return things to people, he wants to help you return things to people.
Kostadis Roussos: He can provide all the people you need to return.
David Mendenhall: I'm Lathander's death? You support Lathander's death. We want the same thing!
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly! Why would there be any confusion? Alright.
Wade Brown: The world is ugly.
Kostadis Roussos: So, while you're sitting there.
Kostadis Roussos: you hear some rumors.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let's… do you hear… you hear,
Kostadis Roussos: Here's somebody whispering that I heard Lathander himself walk the surface to mark her personally.
Kostadis Roussos: You know… you know.
David Mendenhall: Sure, yeah, you should go with that.
Kostadis Roussos: M…
Gary Young: And what do you think?
Wade Brown: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: This is, like, you know…
Gary Young: permit or die, I'm just asking…
Gary Young: And what do they say? What do you say?
Kostadis Roussos: They're kind of like, you know, when people are gossiping about somebody behind their back, and they suddenly realize the person's, like, in their face.
Kostadis Roussos: And goes, huh,
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I, I think that's true. I think that's true. They, they, they, they go.
Kostadis Roussos: I think that's true.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, and doesn't that go for a generous donation?
Kostadis Roussos: And I, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And I, put the basket right under the.
David Mendenhall: Dude, you're turning it into a shakedown!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Isn't that what's true?
Wade Brown: You know, properly religious.
Kostadis Roussos: role and intimidation.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, yeah, I could roll that all day, babe. I've got plus 4. Come on, 15. Boom!
David Mendenhall: I'm gonna get in on this. I'm following my friend's league.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you get?
David Mendenhall: I got an 11.
Gary Young: him the… It keeps her.
Kostadis Roussos: The person's not intimidated, because he feels blessed by Lathander right now.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: 15, he doesn't get intimidated.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I rolled a 17? I rolled a 17, man.
Gary Young: I think it's a D4 for me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll let that one go.
David Mendenhall: Did you watch the…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: inspiring story.
David Mendenhall: Do you want to use your inspiration to increase your roll, Brewberry?
David Mendenhall: Roll a D8.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: D8, okay, let's see, D8.
Gary Young: And you get a 2 for me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: 2?
Gary Young: Yeah, 2 for my Bless, 5?
David Mendenhall: So you get a 20.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So it's 520. There you go, you rolled 17. Now, come on, cuff up some coins.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, just take a note, I have to figure out how much they're gonna cough up.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Didn't… you didn't plan for the… the shakedown?
Kostadis Roussos: Boom!
David Mendenhall: Didn't see that one comment.
Gary Young: down in the church, I mean, like…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: At every opportunity, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: The whole brewery, the whole brewery going around with the thing.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, I might as well…
Wade Brown: Do you normally send over, like, a Cripple Boy or something, like…
Gary Young: We need to not just offer donations, we need to, we need to do the, the whole, business model thing, and, like.
Gary Young: Do the pilot, you know, business rollout.
Gary Young: Make sure.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: By the way, I meant to ask, is there any magic way to plant a bug onto somebody or someplace?
David Mendenhall: So that we.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So that we could spy on them, you know, listen to their…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, you can totally do that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, how does that work?
David Mendenhall: Well, we don't have that spell.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: There. Well, we need to look for that spell, and one of us needs to get it, so that we can listen to, you know, Colin's preview conversations and find out how their business works, so that we can do some sabotage.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: I'd be able to buy a scroll, right?
David Mendenhall: I'm biased.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what we'll use the name.
David Mendenhall: We didn't do that before everyone got together.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, as you're just sort of standing there, Lord Nevermember approaches you.
Gary Young: Welcome to our church.
Kostadis Roussos: And you can see Aldous, like, talking to him nervously next to him.
David Mendenhall: Did you call it our church or my church?
Gary Young: Our church is fine, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Just…
Wade Brown: I won't wait for it.
Gary Young: They're not, like… Branding me as separate from, you know, like, the establishment.
David Mendenhall: I thought you were… I thought your intention was to create a schism.
Gary Young: No, no, I intend to take over the whole… the whole religion, not… Not a great eschism.
Kostadis Roussos: And, as he… he looks at you and smiles.
Kostadis Roussos: And then walks away.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
David Mendenhall: My lord… We're joining you for dinner tonight, isn't that right?
Kostadis Roussos: He smiles at you again.
Kostadis Roussos: Tightly. Tight-lipped.
Gary Young: I looked.
David Mendenhall: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: Aldous turns to you and says, yes, yes, have no worries, have no fears. Dinner, dinner is going to happen. Lord never remembers, it's very busy and preoccupied.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll an insight check.
David Mendenhall: buying.
Gary Young: 21.
Gary Young: Actually, double 21, then.
David Mendenhall: Did you notice?
Kostadis Roussos: you notice that, nevermember, seems particularly appalled with Cullen Sharp.
Wade Brown: Aren't we all?
Gary Young: My lord, is there anything that we can do to assist you?
Gary Young: You may think about that, and if you wish to discuss that tonight at dinner, we'd be very glad to hear of anything we could do to assist you.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, yes, I think I have many questions, as long as we keep in mind the need to circulate the wealth and not hoard it.
Gary Young: To circulate the wall.
Gary Young: Okay.
Wade Brown: wants us He wants the money.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, I mean, yes, so there's,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, and, let's see, is there anything else that happens at this thing?
Gary Young: The Armorsmith, does he get a…
Gary Young: Does it need to get, like.
Gary Young: You know, like, visibly blessed in front of the crowd.
Kostadis Roussos: Tommy, you can go reach out to him and visibly bus him.
Gary Young: Yeah, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Are you not administering the sacrament to everyone?
Gary Young: Anyone who wants.
David Mendenhall: I think… I think you should be calling them up and having them stare into the sun and experience the blinding
David Mendenhall: Light of Luthander.
Gary Young: Sure.
David Mendenhall: So… One by one, everyone comes up and, blinds themselves looking at the sun.
Gary Young: This is the way.
David Mendenhall: I think I will, encourage the crowd.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it's not… it's kind of a…
David Mendenhall: In the… in the right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. There… it turns out that, you've managed to,
Kostadis Roussos: What's the word I'm looking for?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I forgot to do something. So, when you turn around and ask, never member this, the question, is there anything you could do to help?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Never remember, actually, for a moment.
Kostadis Roussos: Looks past the fact that… the fact that, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Colin Sharp seems to be, like, trying to smooge with Vucraidin.
Kostadis Roussos: And, Blueberry seems to be taking his money.
Wade Brown: He gave it willingly.
David Mendenhall: I… I don't like anything about Cullen Sharp. Like, I'm not onto him at all.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, I know, but this is… he's talking to… he's very much focused on Balthine. And he says, I truly do admire your focus on eliminating those who are enemies of Lathander.
Gary Young: Enemies of the light, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I think that is an excellent, focused use of power.
Kostadis Roussos: But I am curious how that message has been received by Lathander's clerics. It seemed to be more about embracing goodness and love for all.
Gary Young: Well, that is the old way.
Wade Brown: Yes, dude.
Gary Young: We need to drive…
David Mendenhall: a tweet.
Gary Young: Or… dedication to the mission and the glory of the Morning Lord, rather than Such passive, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: He smiles, he smiles at you and says, yes, I think, I think, Valfine, your approach to the Morning Lord's powers is something that we should keep talking about. I can see how we could work wonders together.
Gary Young: I look forward to your, partnership.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I look forward to your partnership as well, Valfide. It's important in these trying times that we have people in our… people who see the need for direct action and
Kostadis Roussos: Rather than… anyway, he kind of walks away, he mumbles something about, you know, power and the need for exercising it officially.
Gary Young: What is the Princess Bride's quote of, like, a man of action?
Wade Brown: We are men of action lies did not become us.
Gary Young: Yes, sir.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, whoop, sorry, I just want… I forgot to do that. So is there anything else?
David Mendenhall: achieve.
Gary Young: LA.
David Mendenhall: Now, whatever the effect of blinding half the city.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's not half the city. At this point in time, most people have left, so it's a small group of people.
Gary Young: Oh, that month's sacrament.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, right. And so, they are in ecstasy and happy, so you now have managed to set up a small branch of Lavender searing
Kostadis Roussos: Light.
Gary Young: And,
Kostadis Roussos: in Neverwinter.
David Mendenhall: How many… how many devout followers does Velfine have in this city?
Wade Brown: And how do we invest in the local lens crafters?
Kostadis Roussos: 8.
David Mendenhall: 8?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Oh, those are rookie numbers.
Kostadis Roussos: It's, like, you know, it's a start.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? I mean, between the orcs going around preaching conversion, and the eight people here, and then the temple in whatnot, I mean, you're starting to rack up some serious numbers here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Gary Young: We definitely need to figure out what's going on with the… that works.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, sick of this.
Wade Brown: This way, each of them convert two people, and those convert two people.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: While this is going on, and Soma's kind of like, I don't know, Soma, are you sort of standing next to it, or,
Wade Brown: I mean, I'm observing, like I always do.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay, an exile aesthetic merchant comes to you and says, I… can I, like… License your look.
Kostadis Roussos: Your turtle look.
Wade Brown: I was born with it, I don't know that I have any ownership over it.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I was kind of hoping that we could call it the SOBA line.
Wade Brown: Some are alive.
David Mendenhall: Don't sell out.
Wade Brown: Don't sell out, but wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute. So, I mean, by Greg Cloak's not too far off from a bathrobe. Couldn't we sort of combine production lines here?
David Mendenhall: There's an idea.
Kostadis Roussos: Blueberry,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sorry, I was deep into researching how we could spy on Colin.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now that I have his purse, I'm looking for some sort of magic spell or artifact that I can use to plant a bug on him.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: In the meantime, we're trying to figure out if we can, you know, share productions of robes and soma cloaks.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course.
Kostadis Roussos: So, is this a yes or a no?
Wade Brown: That sounds like a yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I completely trust my partners.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Slide is good with me.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm beginning to see why Wuchrdin and Brewberry got together so well.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a certain naivete about them that is charming.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Perrin is still sitting there.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, and he's… you notice that there's, like, a bunch of people
Kostadis Roussos: Sitting around him, like, he's kind of waiting for you guys to, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Come up to him and get the verification.
Kostadis Roussos: It's kind of looking at you, Burberry, and every so often.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, when you do your terrifying thing, he squirms a little bit, but he seems, waiting to… he's got his witnesses, so to speak.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to go talk to him and find out what… about these witnesses or not?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you approach… you approach them.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's, 3… there's 3, there's… Three guys there.
Kostadis Roussos: They, introduce themselves.
Kostadis Roussos: M… First one… The first one,
Kostadis Roussos: The first one is very enthusiastic, it says, I'm really glad that Perrin's gonna get that, that, that necklace, it's a great symbol of, of the rightful rulers of, of Neverwinter, and… and so on and so forth. Roll a perception check.
Kostadis Roussos: An insight check, or investigation, sorry.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Insight.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's like an infested.
Gary Young: 29th.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's probably better.
Kostadis Roussos: This is with brew… okay, brewery?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: 11.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so you do what, what,
Kostadis Roussos: Balfine picks up is that this guy seems very enthusiastic about the revolution.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh. The, the second person.
Kostadis Roussos: Is a historian, a genealogist, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And he… he's, like, chatting with you and says, oh, Masuma!
Wade Brown: Yes…
Kostadis Roussos: I had a wonderful conversation with Boney.
Wade Brown: Oh, you found my horse.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes. It turns out he was, his interest in, alligander genealogy is almost as encyclopedic as mine.
Wade Brown: Yeah, he had a lot of free time.
Kostadis Roussos: I heard, he told me, he studied the corpses and the dead and the relationships between the dead, and he had some excellent insights. I mean, he's about to go geek out on genealogy if you don't let him…
Wade Brown: I'm here for that.
David Mendenhall: Why would we stop him? This is what we wanted to hear.
Wade Brown: I find these, you know, the provenance of this thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so, I just want you… I cross-referenced Boney's claims and Perrin's claims, and it is, in fact true that Perrin is a descendant, perhaps one of the primary descendants of the Alligander
Kostadis Roussos: family, and I was very pleased to see that Boney was able to,
Kostadis Roussos: To do this. Yeah, to crop us.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sorry, sorry, I remember that.
David Mendenhall: Looking for…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Perhaps…
David Mendenhall: Is there any other…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Primary.
David Mendenhall: that are living.
Kostadis Roussos: Unfortunately, no. Not that I… not that I know of, and Boney more or less confirmed that with me.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why do you say, perhaps, the primary descendant? I don't like this, perhaps. We're not looking for.
Wade Brown: Boney only had corpses to study, right? Like, he doesn't know who's alive.
Kostadis Roussos: So he goes, well, I mean, Mr. Blueberry, I am a scientist.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I'm a historian.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're not a scientist, you're a historian.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Or are you? Which are you? Tomorrow, I talk to you, you'll let you…
Kostadis Roussos: He's about to shit himself in his pants, right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Maybe you're a pole dancer, I don't know.
David Mendenhall: Dude, dude, go count the gold. How much did it take?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll let the man talk.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry.
Wade Brown: You're so good at intimidating everyone.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. He explains that, well, that what he meant by that was that, you know, there can never be 100% certainty, but that he would stake his professional reputation that Perrin is, in fact.
Kostadis Roussos: The true and only claimant for this.
David Mendenhall: Oops. Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You'll prefer…
David Mendenhall: I see what you've done here. The moral dilemma of giving the powerful magical item.
Wade Brown: to an asshole.
David Mendenhall: owner who is evil.
David Mendenhall: But I am gonna stick with my principles.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: And hand it over.
Kostadis Roussos: There, there's a… there's a third person.
David Mendenhall: Oh, there's a third person.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: All three of them.
David Mendenhall: I also want to ask about connections.
Gary Young: Explore the one other option.
Kostadis Roussos: You had 3… you had 3,
David Mendenhall: You said it had to be 3 witnesses? She said.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown: Whatever, then.
Kostadis Roussos: I can't forget the name of this.
Kostadis Roussos: And it's an elderly… yes?
Gary Young: Go ahead, continue, and then…
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's, yeah, let's wrap this up.
Kostadis Roussos: He's an elderly notary clerk who's genuine. He remembers the Alligander family records.
Kostadis Roussos: Role and insight check.
Kostadis Roussos: Or investigation, whichever one you want.
Wade Brown: the heck.
David Mendenhall: 19.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: And you can tell he's visibly frightened.
Kostadis Roussos: And explains that… well, yes, and I just wish to, say that the records, as I recall them, did you clearly put…
Wade Brown: recall.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he pauses and says, when the new administration took over, there was a bit of a purging of records.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: The guy… the guy is clearly being intimidated.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, just to be clear, Neverwinter took over the town and got rid of the alliganders.
Kostadis Roussos: This is, that's… the notary reaches down and says, well, when the Alliganders were removed from power and Lord Neverumber became the first Lord of Neverwinter, well, the removal was a part of a purge.
Wade Brown: What are they paying him? Are you…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We're being manipulated here in thinking that parent is the right heir, is not.
David Mendenhall: So he is the rightful heir.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No.
David Mendenhall: He gets… he gets the necklace. Look, I get it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Like, he's evil.
David Mendenhall: You have to fight.
David Mendenhall: Easy.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: than witnesses.
Gary Young: I don't know that Perrin is evil.
Gary Young: He is certainly intimidated and controlled by people who are evil, but maybe if we can give him a protection racket, then…
Gary Young: You know.
Gary Young: An alternative protection racket.
Wade Brown: I just want to know why he had to, you know… taking his lineage, or prominence at face value, like, why is he paying off this guy, or threatening this, you know, wormy guy?
Kostadis Roussos: So, so, so just, roll your, investigation… what did you… rolled in Insight?
Wade Brown: an insight earlier of…
Kostadis Roussos: Did anybody roll an investigation?
Wade Brown: I'm about to, but I suck at it.
Wade Brown: No. On 18? No.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's not afraid of Perrin.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He's not afraid of parent, okay.
Gary Young: Rolled his Euro.
David Mendenhall: I don't think he's… I don't think he's intimidated, I don't think he's… he's just evil.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's okay. This is gonna come back and bite us in the ass if we…
David Mendenhall: It is! Yes, no, I… Kostadis heard it, so it worked. It's an interesting moral dilemma for us. I appreciate it.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm glad.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm just trying to, you know, cover all sixes.
David Mendenhall: What does it mean if you insist on handing over all the treasure if you're handing it over to people who are evil?
Wade Brown: Even because there's the rightful owners, like, that's the…
David Mendenhall: We are the rightful owners, and I am sticking by my principles.
Kostadis Roussos: Your principal…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, I'm not saying we don't give it back, I'm saying we need to tie it to some sort of, you know,
Wade Brown: reasonable concession?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Slippery…
David Mendenhall: Hello!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Is there… is there a bathroom?
David Mendenhall: Before we did, John.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And, the church…
David Mendenhall: We must impose a concession or not.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Come on, man.
Kostadis Roussos: It's… it's up to you guys. So, he's given you the evidence.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And like I said, the evidence is all genuine.
Kostadis Roussos: Boney has confirmed it with the genealogist. The notary clerk has also confirmed it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll let it go, but mock my words, this is gonna bite us in the ass.
David Mendenhall: It will.
Wade Brown: That's the whole point.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And we're not trying to, you know, take any precaution here or anything, we're just handing him over the knife that he's gonna use to stab us in the back.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's okay.
Wade Brown: He'll probably stab our face.
David Mendenhall: No, it'll be more of a fireball to the face.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, 9, 12D6 fireball.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We're gonna regret this, I'm just saying.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Maybe we could have put a spell on the necklace so that we can disarm it, or, you know, get it back instantly if he uses it.
Wade Brown: private, can't.
David Mendenhall: I don't support that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, Bukrudin, are you handing over the necklace?
David Mendenhall: I… I've already handed it over.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Perrin thanks you greatly.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, go away, get out of my… get out of my sight. I don't want to talk to you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't want to talk to him?
David Mendenhall: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he… well, he, he, he thanks.
David Mendenhall: You need to talk to evil people.
Kostadis Roussos: He's hurt. Would you say that out loud, or do you keep the.
David Mendenhall: intrusive.
Gary Young: No, no, no, no, no, like, he's…
Wade Brown: I love Childish Rupert.
Gary Young: and…
Kostadis Roussos: You're trying to…
Gary Young: I mean, bye.
David Mendenhall: Got your necklace!
David Mendenhall: Goodbye.
Kostadis Roussos: This is… this is childish Rucrative, I mean…
Wade Brown: I love it!
Kostadis Roussos: I talked to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: the guy, I tell him, remember that this was handed over to you in the Temple of the Thunder, you know, this is your chance at redemption. Use it for good.
Wade Brown: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Is, is this…
Wade Brown: The start of your redemption arc.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, okay, he's good. Alright. Okay. So, that's what happens… Spirit.
Wade Brown: We did the right thing, right guys?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No.
Kostadis Roussos: There was no right thing. It was… It was just a thing. The plot would have moved in a wide variety of actions.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: The only right thing we did was…
Gary Young: character.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Watches, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's exactly… you had… we had… you did exactly what your characters would do.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the one thing, you guys didn't do, and I just want to remind you, is that Colin was supposed to tell you who the gnome was.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, that's right.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we've got a… we've got a quest. Talk to a gnome at the docks about why the shipping manifold has stopped working.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah. So who's the gnome, Colin?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, a cone… Colin, smiles at you, I mean, so…
David Mendenhall: Why are we asking this guy?
Kostadis Roussos: because.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Because he knows.
Kostadis Roussos: You… remember, you…
Wade Brown: He's a man who can get things.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me be clear. There are two sources for the information. One is you could go to the counting house.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We will.
Kostadis Roussos: And the other is, Colin promised to get you the information. So, which one do you want to go… do you want to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, we're gonna do both.
Gary Young: That's right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: First, I ask Colin, then I go to the counting house and, you know, cross-check the info, and see if Colin.
David Mendenhall: I am walk… I have want nothing to do with Cullen. If you're talking to him, I'm not there.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fair. That's… that's fair. Colin… so, Blueberry, you show up there. Colin's a bit disappointed that
Kostadis Roussos: you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, I don't care.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Vukra didn't… sorry, my… I was,
Kostadis Roussos: About to burp. Brewberry's, he's disappointed to see that Brewberry's, that Brewerdin's not with you.
Kostadis Roussos: And he says, how can I help you?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Whoa… Remember, I asked you to find the gnome's name for me, as David.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, yes, yes. And of course, far be it from me to not deliver on what you've asked for.
Kostadis Roussos: As I said, the House Margaster always delivers.
Wade Brown: I think it's a little.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Or if you could FedEx this info to me, my friend, that'd.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just… I need… I need to get the name, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Trying to get the new name.
Kostadis Roussos: Burgos, well, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: His name is Bimble Knackle.
Wade Brown: Oh, no names.
David Mendenhall: though.
Kostadis Roussos: You're not there.
David Mendenhall: Timbo.
Kostadis Roussos: Bimble. Bimble.
David Mendenhall: Bimbo, I got it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Name is great, location is better, and if I could know who he works for as well, that'd be awesome.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do you know?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, does he know?
Kostadis Roussos: So, what is it that you wanted to know? Like, where is he?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Where can I find Disk Gnome, and who does he work for?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Zero investigation. Well done. I love it.
David Mendenhall: Not your moment.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I need to find out…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why would we roll for investigation? Is willingly giving us this information?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, you know, there's no, there's no investigation,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Maybe insight to see if he's lying.
David Mendenhall: I don't think he's lying.
Kostadis Roussos: He's not lying.
Kostadis Roussos: However, I'm assuming one of you,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, too late to give the info.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my goodness.
David Mendenhall: Bibimo? Bibmo?
David Mendenhall: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Bimble.
David Mendenhall: Bimble… Bimble Knackle?
David Mendenhall: I like bimbo better.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: So, what we can tell from this gnomish name is that he is of very low class stature, because his name is very short.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: How can we tell that?
Wade Brown: It's his name is George.
Gary Young: It has a very small number of syllables.
Gary Young: See if…
Wade Brown: It's like judging a scotch.
Gary Young: And that's Raponium captured alphabucks.
Gary Young: Like, he's of a high class.
David Mendenhall: I, I did not know that.
Gary Young: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, okay. So… Really?
Gary Young: I just made that up.
David Mendenhall: Very convincing!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, you sold me on it.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so, yes, so they describe a, Bimble, Bimble, Bimble is, is described as a, very fastidious gnome,
Kostadis Roussos: That, worked.
Kostadis Roussos: the machinery of, work the machinery, but that Colin doesn't know anything more.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He doesn't know who hired him, who he's working for.
Kostadis Roussos: Where.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He lives, where we can find him.
Kostadis Roussos: Unfortunately, we merely took over the… we were not involved, and perhaps if we had been, the Commission's transportation system would have continued to be working.
Wade Brown: Perhaps.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So who was involved?
David Mendenhall: as well.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm asking, who hired this guy?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, but the Houseman Gaster was not involved in the hiring of Mimble. We just heard of his name after the machinery stopped working.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And you didn't recommend him to the people who hired him, or anything like that?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, how can I detect if he's telling the truth?
David Mendenhall: She's telling the truth.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Certainly doubt it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Mine is just evil.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, the word is not always black and white, Bucherton. It's mostly gray.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, well, I'm a celestial.
Wade Brown: True.
Kostadis Roussos: Hell yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, so we got the name, not the location. Alright, maybe the counting house will have the location, and who commissioned him.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: looking for.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We'll find the connection.
Kostadis Roussos: You'll find the connections at the theory.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Still need to find a way to spy on Colin, though.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll figure.
David Mendenhall: We're not high enough level for that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're not by getting it?
Kostadis Roussos: This is not… yeah, this is setting stuff up, is…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, I got… okay, so that's… that's it. That's all the things that happen here. We've exhausted this area, so what would you like to do,
David Mendenhall: So, if you want, you have a bag of his?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on.
David Mendenhall: over.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: It doesn't matter.
David Mendenhall: Do you want to put one of the sending stones in the bag, and then give it back to them?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What's the… what's the sending stone again?
Wade Brown: Basically, a microphone.
David Mendenhall: It's a bit of a microphone.
Wade Brown: Like a walkie-talkie.
Kostadis Roussos: But can you force it to record on the other side, or…
Kostadis Roussos: you can now send a message to Cassian whenever you want.
Kostadis Roussos: if I recall from your abilities, right, Dave?
David Mendenhall: Well, if I… if I cast sending, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh…
David Mendenhall: But Ascending Stone has a permanent enchantment on it, and we have to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So we disguise the sending stone as a coin, and then we cast Magic Mouth on another coin, And…
David Mendenhall: Why is it how? I don't have a permanent polymorph. I only have to… I'm not high enough level for that.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, we'll find some magic shop where they can do that for us, for a…
David Mendenhall: I thought we needed to give the bag back to him now.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, no, not now, later.
David Mendenhall: Oh, you're gonna do it later, okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, yeah. And so the coin that has Magic Mouth cast on it will just repeat the last, you know, 5 minutes of conversation based on the trigger, and then it will tell it to the sending stone that can send the message to us.
David Mendenhall: Blueberry, you've gotten a lot smarter.
David Mendenhall: This one… this is all you… this is beyond me, man. This is all you.
Kostadis Roussos: This is levels… I mean, Brewberry, ever since Brewberry got screwed over by a little… like, by a ferry that gave him, things, he's become increasingly paranoid.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, huh.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: Anita.
David Mendenhall: I need a headband of intellect.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It enhances my spycraft.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And then we can discover details about their business, and we can act where it will hurt them the most, you know?
David Mendenhall: Hi.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And forced…
Kostadis Roussos: But with Guardian Barbarian, I mean, I'm gonna go with this. I like this.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm on a mission, man.
Kostadis Roussos: you're on a mission, right? I mean.
David Mendenhall: A mission from Luthander.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, okay.
Wade Brown: Mission to sell bathrobes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Gary Young: Fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: outside the Temple of Lathander, I presume.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And as you stand outside there… So I'm a little bit…
Kostadis Roussos: That's it. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: The clouds disperses, a colonade gives cover, quiet conversation, the city wakes, is now waking to the news of what's happened, the arrival of the new band that Rukerdin, the legendary musician, is a member of.
Kostadis Roussos: That Lord nevermember spoke privately to Valfine.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, that also made the… seemed to be very positive in his reaction to her.
Kostadis Roussos: The one thing that you could do is you could… we could wrap up with the conversation with the priest… with the,
Kostadis Roussos: the mu- the bank.
Kostadis Roussos: The banker. The banker. The banker.
Kostadis Roussos: Or in vents.
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Gary Young: He's seen the presentation and can see the reception that the… that the business will.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, no, he also has… you also tasked him with finding information.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, Blueberry wanted to go to the counting house.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so you head over to the counting house.
Kostadis Roussos: Where, hold on, I just lost my Roll20. You head over to the counting house where Oren Vance, is sitting, he sees Blueberry walk in and just, like, literally, you know, kind of has that look of, oh, shit, pain in his face, and then quickly puts on a… the most professional of professional smiles.
Kostadis Roussos: And invites you…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: rent.
Kostadis Roussos: My good friend, Mr. Brewberry, I am delighted to see you.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And so am I, because I know you have the information I'm looking for.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he goes, yes, well, this is not… this is not a great secret. I mean, the Commission, as you know, was responsible for,
Kostadis Roussos: Trade and revenue growth in the area, and simply said that the manifold experienced a maintenance failure.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Somebody. Can you be more precise?
Kostadis Roussos: Not somebody. The commission. The commission.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: commission, okay? Yes. Who specifically in the commission said this, do you know?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it was a public announcement by the… I… I will get you a name, just there was a… there was a commission, who… who announced it, because, the, the, that's the word I'm looking for…
Kostadis Roussos: This was part of the… this was… this, of course, caused great constidation, as you… since you are now planning to be a man of wealth, and I'm sure Lenene, as a wealth management consultant, has already communicated this to you.
Kostadis Roussos: But the Commission was involved in managing the trade, and all the major houses had shares in the Commission.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right. The Metroid T holder being…
Kostadis Roussos: Lord, nevermember, is my understanding, but the Commission's membership was a tightly guarded secret.
Kostadis Roussos: So, they're involved in all the businesses around Neverwinter, and have definitely been the method by which Lord Nevermember has been using to grow, but this is not secret, Blueberry, I…
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So my good friend, my good.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I'm.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Wha… yep.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm not… I'm not… before you interrupt me one more time, let me just, so, what happened was that the commission described… says that this is a maintenance failure. They hired a technician.
Kostadis Roussos: Who,
Kostadis Roussos: Who has been… who investigated it, but, there's… we… we… but the commission said he found nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: But they have never proffered his name, or who he worked for, or where he is. For all we know, he never did exist, but I could not imagine why they would say that. After all, the manifold was a critical part of the revenue
Kostadis Roussos: that the Commission generated for the City of Neverwinter, and this has opened up opportunity for new players in trade.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, that was a very long sentence for very little information.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: But, if you were me, and trying to find this mysterious gnome, who would you talk to at the commission to find out?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I don't know if he goes to commission. He turns pale at that idea.
Kostadis Roussos: Role and insight, Chuck.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I suck at insight.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: How are one of you rolling in sight?
Kostadis Roussos: Or history.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Not good.
Gary Young: 28 inside.
Kostadis Roussos: Blueberry's question triggers a thought in Valfinay, she, in their time in Menzo-Brunsen, she always knew that if somebody needed to go find somebody, the Harpers were the people you wanted to go talk to.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: The hoppers, okay. Wait.
Gary Young: I knew from my time in Mensa-Barranza.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, because you kept… because the Lothian clerics would be periodically killing and purging Harper agents who got themselves involved.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Just… just roll with it.
Gary Young: Which is the correct way, yes.
Wade Brown: You do.
Kostadis Roussos: Is it… and since they're.
David Mendenhall: from the…
Kostadis Roussos: Overbrite, so since you see from the overbright, and you've seen how unruthless everybody is about securing information, you've concluded that they must be the information purveyors in the overbright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, one last question.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, I mean, given how, you know, ineffective they were, but that they kept coming, you figure they should show up somewhere. And so, yes, that's kind of my… that's kind of my reverse reasoning about why you would assume that's that.
Gary Young: So we also do have an audience with Lord Nevermember. If he was part of this council, we could…
Gary Young: Ask him.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so… so yes, one… one option is, the Harpers. The other, he unfortunately says, I, I don't know,
Kostadis Roussos: I can't help you beyond that, unfortunately, Mr. Blueberry. The information I have and the resources of the Counting House are more in the financial management rather than the investigatory. But I do think, you know, I would say that it was an unfortunate malfunction.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, sounds to me like you need to rethink your strategy, my friend. I mean, finance is at the root of everything, and so is information. So how can you make more money without good information? I don't know. Anyway…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll find out who this gnome is, I'll find out who hired him, and I'll get to the bottom of this. Last question, would you have any idea why…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Lord, nevermembers people would tell me that they had nothing to do in the hiring of this,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: gnome technician.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, Housemar Gaster said that, not…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, yeah, Housemont Gaster, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, it goes, it goes, oh, oh, no, no, no, no, he, he looks, he's very confused. Helspergaster would have nothing to do with the hiring of this, this individual.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Aren't they on the commission?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What's my gaster.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, to the best of my knowledge, no, this has been the source of much contention in the city.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Then there's something I'm missing here, I don't get it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, Housemarghaster is not on the commission. The commission hired the gnome, who sabotaged the device, And the main…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: beneficiaries. Benefit from this is how Smock Master.
Wade Brown: I mean.
Kostadis Roussos: Or there's something else… or there's something else going on.
Wade Brown: Pretty easy for them to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Connection witness at middleman.
Wade Brown: or Etsy, right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, yeah, so there must be a connection.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Between House Market.
David Mendenhall: and somebody on the team.
David Mendenhall: All parts.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Dave has had enough of this.
David Mendenhall: Ding.
Wade Brown: He's got the yarn board out already.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Carrie, if… Sorry, so I just… I completely flailed on this. Belfine doesn't know about the Harpers, right? I mean, she… does she… does she suggest us secret services, or, like, how… what would she suggest in terms of how you would go find someone?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you okay with the… are you okay… are you okay with the heartburn narrative or not? That's, like…
Gary Young: I don't know, like, I feel like, you know, the way to find someone is to put a, a hit out on them, and then it becomes someone else's problem to find them.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that… But the striker's gotta have some…
Wade Brown: network.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, fine. That's what we'll go with canonically.
Gary Young: The Assassin's Guild always knows how to find their targets, right?
David Mendenhall: Athens Guild.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, I will go with that.
Wade Brown: dry.
David Mendenhall: very first edition.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Assassin's Guild.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I like it.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you say… do you blurt that out loud? Like, kind of like, I know how to… you go, yes, you're right. We would go to the Assassin Guild.
Gary Young: I mean, it's just natural.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
David Mendenhall: Volcine.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on. When, when, Colin… sorry, the Oren Vance hears that and kind of turns pale, looks at you, for a moment, he's like, you just, of course!
David Mendenhall: He jests. As you know, he's a cleric of Lithander.
Wade Brown: They are jokers.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, my friend is just kidding. And thank you for doing me this favor and finding this information. Know that if you've done me a favor, I'll do you a favor.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. Blueberry, as I've said, we are very happy.
David Mendenhall: Doing quid pro quo now?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's right. That's how it works, my friend.
David Mendenhall: That is not how it works!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's how it works in Brube's world.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, you be nice to him, he'd be nice to you.
David Mendenhall: You should be nice to everybody!
Wade Brown: And they'll be nice back.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: acting favors, you know, then I can be Neverwinter's godfather.
David Mendenhall: Centrum of you.
Kostadis Roussos: just to be clear, like, the way I see it is, Brewberry… I mean, just so we're all on the same page, Brewberry was a part of a tribe, he trusted somebody, they gave him some,
Kostadis Roussos: Goodberry, they thought they were giving him some Goodberries, it was actually something that knocked him out. As a result of being knocked out, you know, something was stolen, an artifact was stolen. Brewberry was accused of, you know, not doing his job, kicked out of his tribe. He ended up in,
Kostadis Roussos: in Neverwinter, barely… fell in love with Mukridan's original music, because it appealed to his distorted soul, and since then, you know, as he's gained more and more power, he's become more and more paranoid about things that work and don't work, and how reality fits together.
David Mendenhall: Yes, paranoid. Paranoid sounds right to me, yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Does that, does that capture, of, stephane?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, yes, but then, in Brewberry's mind, people…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: do things when they are motivated to do something. So again, I'm just giving this banker motivation, you know. Okay. He's helped me, I can help him.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And then, and then, you know, the…
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's good.
David Mendenhall: Give him an offer he can't refuse, Burbury.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's always good to have a banker's friend, you know, or a friend.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so next week we'll do with Soma and her turtle soup.
Wade Brown: Torto soup!
David Mendenhall: Alright, goodbye.
Wade Brown: Good night. My dog's getting pushy. Alright guys, it was great.
Kostadis Roussos: It was great fun. I hope you enjoyed that, Barry.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Absolutely. Great sermon, Gary.
Wade Brown: Yeah, fantastic.
Gary Young: Okay, bet.
Kostadis Roussos: That was, that was awesome. That was, that was, very well designed.
Gary Young: incrementic.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Pirate, that's firing.
Kostadis Roussos: Inspiring. Inspiring. Yes, and you now have… you now have another branch of Lathander's searing… Light.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you. In, in, Neverwinter.
Gary Young: I will make sure not to abuse that privilege.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And I will make sure you will.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, sir, take care.